A Finding Aid to the Charles Rand Penney Papers, 1923-1994, bulk 1945-1994, in the Archives of American Art AAA.pennchar
Archives of American Art
- Art Collection Files, 1923-1994; Series 1; 22.7 Linear feet Boxes 1-23, OV 24
  - Walkowitz, Abraham, General, 1957-1994 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Walkowitz, Abraham, Marjorie Peabody Waite Award, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Weber, Max, 1961-1994 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Weinrib, David, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Wengenroth, Stow, 1970-1985 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Wilcox, Frank N., 1964-1988 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Wilke, Ulfert (Box 22)
    - General, 1969-1984 (Box 22, Folder 28-29)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1977 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Death of the Artist, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Hancher Auditorium Poster 1972-1982, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1971 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Retrospective Exhibition, (1983) (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Thick and Thin (1967), circa 1960s (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - "Ulfert Wilke: Recent Works" (1970-1971), 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Wilke Gift Wrap, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Wines, James (Box 23)
    - General, 1965-1986 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Best Products Company, 1980-1988 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Ghost Parking Lot Project (1978) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Midnight Disc II (1963), 1964-1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Sculpture in the Environment Group (SITE), 1983-1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Skysaw (1979), Purchase, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Witkin, Isaac, 1978-1992 (Box 23)
    - General, 1979-1985 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence from artist to Penney, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Hamilton Gallery, 1979-1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Hirschl and Adler Modern, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Locks Gallery, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Periodical, Arts Magazine, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Wyeth, N.C., 1988 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Yarwood, Walter, 1962-1984 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Yoder, Marjorie S., circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Young, Mahonri Mackintosh, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Youngerman, Jack, 1965-1993 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Yunkers, Adja, 1967-1994 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Zorach, William, 1974-1990 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Toronto 20 (1965) (Box 23)
    - General, 1965-1972 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Burton, Dennis, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Bush, Jack, 1970-1985 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Coughtry, Graham, 1966-1979 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Curnoe, Greg, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Etrog, Sorel, circa 1960s (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Gorman, Richard, circa 1960s (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Hedrick, Robert, 1973-1981 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Kureiek, William, 1967-1980 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Levine, Les, 1967-1981 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Markgraf, Waltraud, circa 1960s (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Markle, Robert, circa 1960s-1978 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Meredith, John, circa 1960s (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Nakamura, Kazuo, circa 1960s-1974 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Raynor, Gordon, circa 1960s (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Ronald, William, 1965-1978 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Snow, Michael, 1966-1981 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Teitelbaum, Maschel, circa 1960s-1978 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Weiland, Joyce, 1967-1978 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Material Related to Exhibitions Featuring the Charles Rand Penney Art Collection, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Oversized Material from Alexander Calder, James Goodman Gallery from Box 4, Folder 46, circa 1966 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Material from Jack Levine, Midtown Payson Galleries, Inc. from Box 13, Folder 21, 1990 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Material from Alex Liberman, General from Box 13, Folder 22, 1970-1992 (Box OV 24)
- Catalogs of the Charles Rand Penney Art Collection, 1966-1991; Series 2; 0.2 Linear feet Box 23
  The series is arranged in chronological order.
  Found here are catalogs from exhibitions that featured artwork from Charles Rand Penney's collection of art.
  - Catalogs, 1966-1979 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Catalogs, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Catalogs, 1983-1991 (Box 23, Folder 44)